Peyton Rous Papers 1909-1970 Mss.B.R77
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, ca.1917-1970; 47.0 Linear feet (Box 1-85)
  - Century Association
    - Mackenzie, G M
    - Marquand, John P
    - Sachs, Paul J
    - Merrill, Edwin G
    - Milliken, Arthur
    - Parker, Franklin
    - Rose, H Wyckliffe
    - Smith, Henry Clapp
    - Wiley, Alexander
    - Greet, Cabell
    - McEwen, Currier
    - Briggs, W H
  - Cerino, Lawrence E
  - Chadwick
  - Chalmers, Thomas
  - Chamberlain, Mrs. Peter
    - Armstrong, Donald
  - Chambers, Robert
    in re The Society of Cellular Biology
  - Chapman, E J C
  - Charaka Club
    - Cole, Rufus
    - Collins, Joseph
    - Craig, Howard Reid
    - Emerson, Haven
    - Gerster, John C A
    - Hanger, Franklin M
    - Kennedy, Foster
    - Malloch, Archibald
    - Oliver, Wade W
    - Rake, Geoffroy
    - Keyes, Edward L
    - Paine, Thomas, Fl., 1946
    - Lambert, Samuel W
    - Wood, Casey A
    - Cohn, Alfred E
    - "The Devil and the Doctors."
    - A talk by P. Rous, Jan. 17, 1951
    - "The Disagreement among Doctors"
    - A Talk by P. Rous
  - Charipper, Harry A
  - Charles, W B
  - Charrette, E E
  - Chase, Emery G
  - Chase, George
  - Chase, Herman B
  - Chatterjee, H N
  - Chelson, Richard
  - Chemical Corn Exchange Bank
  - Chemical Corps Medical Laboratories
  - Cheraskin, E
  - Cherbonnier, A Victor
  - Chesney, Alan M
  - Chester Beatty Research Institute
  - Chicken Tumor
    - Andrewes, C H
    - Baker, Stephen L
    - Barbanti, Prof.
    - Campo, A J
      Typed 8-14-73
    - Cary, L R
    - Shope, Richard E
    - Coley, William B
    - Du Nouy, P Le Comte
    - Eggers, A E
    - Feldman, William H
    - Friede, K
    - Hyde, Roscoe R
    - Ivy, A C
    - Hyman, Julius
    - Jobling, James W
    - Kolmer, John A
    - Lewis, W K
    - Miller, John K
    - Passey, R D
    - Patton, W D
    - Rouse, William J
    - Saborido, J
    - Shrum, Edison E
    - Shwartzman, Gregory
    - Tenbroeck, Carl
    - Webb, Robert A
    - Weintraub, A D
    - Woglam, William H
    - Seigfried, O
    - Zwick, W
    - Gentil, F
    - Athias, Mark
    - Bayon, H P
    - Bischeghe, Vicenzo
    - Bleyer, L
    - Reimann, Hobart A
    - Califano, Luigi
    - Cutler, Oran
    - Engle, J L
    - Krumbhaar, E B
    - Kolmer, John A
    - Franchino, R G
    - Funk, Casimir
    - Goodpasture, Ernest W
    - Holmes, Mrs. B A
    - Karczag, Ladislav
    - Kirby, Daniel B
    - Kritschewsky, I
    - Locke, Arthur
    - Russell, F F
    - Marine, David
    - McIver, Monroe A
    - McJenkin, F A
    - McKinley, E B
    - Morton, J J
    - Mueller, J Howard
    - Rivers, T M
    - Wood, Francis Carter
    - Sordelli, A
    - Sperti, George
    - Becker, S W
    - Fiset, P E
    - Claude, Albert
    - Meyer, K F
    - Amoss, H L
    - Aragao
    - Aschoff, Ludwig
    - Banting, F G
    - Barr, David P
    - Beatti, Manuel
    - Benedict, Stanley R
    - Blumenthal, Ferdinand
    - Pettit, R T
    - Burrows, Montiose T
    - Campbell Soups Co.
    - Carrel, Alexis
    - Clairmont, P
    - Cori, Carl F
    - Crowell, B C
    - D'Agata, G
    - Dale, H H
    - Dandy, Walter E
    - Dean, H R
    - Deelman, H T
    - Drbohlav, Jaroslav
    - Tyzzer, E E
    - Fialho, Amadeu
    - Read, Florence
    - Furth, Otto
    - Gaylord, H R
    - Gundisalva, M
    - Kelling, Gedrg
    - Kraus, R
    - Kuczynski, Max H
    - Landsteiner, Karl
    - Leake, Chauncey D
    - Lewis, Margaret Reed
    - Lewis, Warren H
    - Lipshutz, Dr.
    - Llambias, J
    - London, Julian
    - Luger, A
    - MacCallum, W G
    - Mawas, J
    - Meyer, O
    - Morton, John
    - Murray, J A
    - Nagayo, M
    - Ogata, Tomosaburo
    - Parodi, Umberto
    - Passey
    - Pearl, Raymond
      typed 8-16-73
    - Pentimalli, F
    - Peyre
    - Pfeiffer, R
    - Prudden, T Mitchell
    - Raposo, Luis Simoes
    - Redway
    - Amaral, Afraino Do
    - Roskin, Gr
    - Roussy, Gustave
    - Schinz, H R
    - Sehing
    - Scott, Joseph M
    - Scott, Mary A R
    - Simon, Charles E
    - Simpson, Burton T
    - Sirvent, E H
    - Smith, Theobald
    - Stokes, Adrian
    - Teutschlaender
    - Warburg, Otto
    - Waterman, N
    - Weinberg, M
    - Wilson, J A
    - Wolff, L M
    - Wood, Francis C
    - Zinsser, Hans
  - Chicken Sarcoma
    - Hoffstadt, Rachel E
    - Wyeth, George
    - Claude, Albert
  - Child, Charles G, III
  - Childs, Starling W
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1937
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Brickner, Richard M
    - Atwell, Wayne J
    - Salter, William T
    - Wolfe, J M
    - Bryan, W R
    - Loeb, Leo
    - Burr, Harold S
    - Newman, Melvin S
    - Murlin, John R
    - MacCallum, W G
    - Hisaw, Frederick L
    - Bergmann, Werner
    - Brickner, Richard M
    - Burwell, C Sidney
    - Aub, Joseph C
    - Collis P. Huntington Memorial Hospital
    - Barry, Adrienne
    - Cumming, C.N. Wentworth
    - Haagensen, C D
    - Kipper, H B
    - Little, C C
    - Palmer, A J
    - Rendle, J A
    - Smith, Arthur H
    - Weissenberg, Richard
    - Winslow, Maurice
    - Thompson, Bernardo S
  - Childs, Memorial Fund, 1938
    - Allen, Edgar
    - Ames, Mrs. Carolyn Stetson
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Anderson, R J
    - Chidester, F E
    - Ewing, James
    - Gasser, H S
    - Jones, D F
    - Kennaway, E L
    - Wigram, Kenneth
    - Little, C. C
    - Kennaway, E L
    - Opie, Eugene L
    - Oughterson, A W
    - Cowgill, George R
    - Belkin, Morris
    - Baffel, Daniel
    - Chidester, F E
    - Ewing, James
    - Gye, W E
    - Hammett, Frederick S
    - Jones, Donald F
    - Cushing, Harvey
    - McLeod, James C
    - Tauber, Henry
    - Nebel, B R
    - Millikan, Robert A
    - Kellogg, W K
    - Duran-Reynals, F
    - Chambers, Robert
    - Lawrence, John H
    - Sigel, Harry
    - Ingleby, Helen
    - Wood, Francis C
    - Burr, H S
    - Loeb, Leo
    - MacCallum, W G
    - Bergmann, Werner
    - Jurka, Edith M
    - Dochez, A Raymond
    - Haagensen, Cushman D
    - Harrison, Ross G
    - Northrop, John H
    - Winternitz, M C
    - Morton, John J
    - Bruce, William F
    - Goldfeder, Anna
    - Goldstein, Samuel
      typed 8-20-73
    - Scheff, George
    - Slye, Maud
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1939
    - Andrewes, C H
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Ingoolsted, Elizabeth
    - Cramer, W
    - Evans, Herbert M
    - Morton, John J
    - Pincus, Gregory
    - Bergmann, Werner
    - Graves, Robert W
    - Woodhall, Barnes
    - Berry, George P
    - Syverton, Jerome T
    - Gardner, William U
    - Opie, Eugene L
    - Fowler, Ona Meigs
    - Hall, B Vincent
    - Kirschbaum, Arthur
    - Lankenau Hospital Research Institute
    - Newman, Melvin S
    - Sulzberger, Marion B
    - Salomon, Kurt
    - Cowdry, E V
    - Gye, W E
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Webster, J.H. Douglas
    - Chibnall, A C
    - Weiss, Charles
    - Sugar, Istvan
    - Stark, Mary B
    - Smith, Lawrence W
    - Schindler, Richard
    - Popoff, N W
    - Papanicolaou, George N
    - Lipschutz, Alexander
    - Bagg, Halsey J
    - Ellinger, Frederick P
    - Young, Hugh H
    - Wood, Francis C
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1940
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Cowdry, E V
    - Berry, G P
    - Syverton, Jerome
    - Childs, Starling
    - Wood, Francis Carter
    - Zirkle, R E
    - Bergmann, Werner
    - Giderner, Alfred
    - Landauer, Walter
    - Lawrence, John H
    - West, Philip M
    - Burr, Harold S
    - Cohen, Philip P
    - Forbus, Wiley D
    - Jones, Donald F
    - Loeb, Leo
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Winternitz, M C
    - Schram, M W S
    - Heilbrunn, L V
    - Simon, Sidney L
    - Opie, Eugene L
    - Vinson, Carl G
    - Fogg, Lloyd C
    - Strode, George K
    - Warren, Shields
    - Aub, Joseph C
    - Fieser, Louis F
    - Gardner, William U
    - Anderson, R J
    - Smith, David P
    - Casey, Albert E
    - Gunn, C K
    - Murlin, John R
    - Reynals
    - Bernstein, Felix
    - Casey, Albert E
    - Forkner, Claude E
    - Velick, Sidney F
    - Wrinch, Dorothy M
    - Hecht, Hugo
    - Thomas, W B S
    - Welker, William H
    - Werthessen, Nicholas T
    - White, Abraham
    - Brues, Austin M
    - Cohn, Waldo E
    - Duran-Reynals, F
    - Yale U., School of Medicine
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1941
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Cowdry, E V
    - Gowen, John W
    - Wood, Francis Carter
    - Harrison, Ross G
    - Hueper, W C
    - Glaser, Otto C
    - Morton, John J
    - Shope, Richard E
    - Smith, George M
    - Ladd, William S
    - Winternitz, M C
    - Robson, William
    - Lund, Charles C
    - Mueller, J Howard
      typed 8-23-73
    - Cohen, Philip P
    - Stern, Kurt G
    - Belkin, Morris, et al
    - Harvey, Samuel C
    - Burr, Harold S
    - Eisenhardt, Louise
    - Lawrence, John S
    - Salter, William T
    - Bergmann, Werner
    - Lawrence, John H
    - Loeb, Leo
    - McCutcheon, Morton
    - Paul, John R
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Dunning, Wilhemina F
    - Curtis, Maynie R
    - Moore, Robert A
    - Wearn, Joseph T
    - Tannenbaum, Albert
    - Amer. Ass'n of Pathologists and Bacteriologists
    - Warren, Shields
    - Fieser, Louis F
    - Memorial Hospital, N.Y.C.
    - Gardner, William U
    - Jackson Memorial Laboratory
    - Anderson, Rudolph J
    - Gasser, Herbert S
    - Opie, Eugene L
    - Pincus, Gregory
    - Menkin, Valy
    - Braunstein, Albert
    - Kirschbaum, Arthur
    - Barclay, Albert H
    - Malisoff, William M
    - Hollander, Franklin
    - Eisen, Milton J
    - Hooker, Charles W
    - Pfeiffer, Carroll A
    - Wachtel, Henry K
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1942
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Meader, Ralph G
    - Walcott, F C
    - Winternitz, M
    - Ward, George Gray
    - Heyman, J
    - Salter, William T
    - Harvey, Samuel C
    - Aub, Joseph C
    - Brues, Austin M
    - Cohn, Waldo E
    - Cowdry, E V
    - Hollander, Franklin
    - Hooker, C W
    - Pfeiffer, C A
    - Jackson Memorial Laboratory
    - Kirschbaum, Arthur
    - Loeb, Leo
    - Blumenthal, H T
    - Long, C N H
    - Memorial Hospital, N.Y.C.
    - Moore, Robert A
    - Sturtevant, Julian M
    - Tannenbaum, Albert
    - Visscher, M B
    - Warren, Shields
    - Fieser, Louis F
    - Zimmerman, Harry M
    - Menkin, Valy
    - Gilman, C Malcolm B
    - Hunt, Thomas Elwood
    - Hotchkiss, Cora B
    - Stern, Kurt
    - Lipschutz, Alexander
    - Greene, Harry S.N.
    - Biskind, Morton
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1943
    - Meader, Ralph G
    - Taylor, Alfred
    - Morton, John J
    - Winternitz, M C
    - Harvey, Samuel C
    - Selye, Hans
    - Long, C N H
    - Hooker, C W
    - Salter, William T
    - Yale University School of Medicine
    - Greene, H.S.N.
    - Zimmerman, Harry M
    - Memorial Hospital, N.Y.C.
    - Opie, Eugene L
    - Jackson Memorial Laboratory
    - Menkin, Valy
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope
    - Gardner, William U
    - Strong, Leonell C
    - Pfeiffer, C A
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1944
    - Cowdry, E V
    - Meader, Ralph G
    - Currie, J P
    - Lawrence, E A
    - Salter, William T
    - Trumbull, Merlin L
    - Bell, A L L
    - Greene, Harry S.N.
    - Yale U. School of Medicine
    - Lund, Paul Kenneth
      typed 8-11-73
    - Murphy, E D
    - Duran-Reynals, F
    - Furth, J
    - Harvey, Samuel C
    - Memorial Hospital, N.Y.C.
    - Jackson Memorial Laboratory
    - Opie, Eugene L
    - Kirschbaum, A
    - Kidd, John G
    - Bittner, J J
    - Green, R G
    - Gorbman, A
    - Ory, E M
    - Childs, Starling W
    - Smith, George M
    - Hooker, C W
    - Gorbman, Aubrey
    - Wu, S D
    - Stowell, Robert E
    - Murphy, Edwin Daniel
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1945
    - Childs, Starling W
    - Macdonald, Mary C
    - Meader, Ralph, G
    - Smith, George M
    - Harvey, T S
    - Yale U. School of Medicine
    - Salter, William T
    - Gorbman, A
    - Lawrence, E A
    - Dunning, Wilhelmina F
    - Schiff, Leon
    - Rusch, H P
    - Miller, J A
    - Kaplan, Henry S
    - Wangensteen, Owen H
    - Bittner, J J
    - Green, R G
    - Barnum, C P Jr.
    - Kirscbaum, Arthur
    - Opie, Eugene
    - Jackson Memorial Laboratory
    - Cowdry, E V
    - Goodman, Louis S
    - Wintrobe, Maxwell
    - Schneider, Walter C
    - Moore, Carl R
    - Conference on Steroid Hormones in Relation to Abnormal Growth
    - Gardner, W U
    - Heard, R D H
    - Hooker, Charles W
    - White, A
    - Greene, H S N
    - Nathanson, Ira T
    - Barron, E.S. Guzman
    - Duran-Reynals, F
    - Fruton, Joseph S
    - Jahiel, Richard
    - Memorial Hospital
    - Stowell, Robert E
    - Strong, Leonell C
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1946
    - Anderson, Rudolph J
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Rhoads, C P
    - Meader, Ralph G
    - Kennaway, E L
    - Menkin, Valy
    - Bothereau, N R
    - Gardner, William U
    - Strong, Leonell C
    - Duran-Reynal, F
    - Baker, Carl G
    - Turner, Joseph C
    - Engelbreth-Holm, Julius
    - Cancer Research Journal
    - Lederberg, Joshua
    - Karnofsky, David A
    - Homburger, Freddy
    - Memorial Hospital, N.Y.C.
    - Jackson Memorial Hospital
    - Bayne-Jones, S
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1947
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Berenblum, I
    - Warren, Shields
    - Mester, Elizabeth
    - Meader, Ralph
    - Rogers, Stanfield
    - Gasser, Herbert S
    - Harvey, Samuel C
    - Gorbman, Aubrey
    - Atkinson, William B
    - Lederberg, Joshua
    - Gregoire, Charles
    - Opie, Eugene L
    - Jorgens, Joseph
    - Burkholder, Paul R
    - Wagtendonk, Willem Johann von
    - Murphy, Edwin D
    - Wagensteen, Owen H
    - Jackson Memorial Laboratory
    - Green, Robert G
    - Kaplan, Henry S
    - Sokal, Joseph E
    - Kidd, John G
    - Haddow, Alexander
    - Kennaway, E L
    - Goetsch, John B
    - Trentin, John J
    - Anlyan, A John
      Typed 9-17-73
    - Baker, Carl G
    - Cerecedo, Leopold R
    - Lu, Chen-Shan
    - Mark, Donald D
    - Clark, Janet H
    - Demerec, Milislav
    - Greene, Harry S.N.
    - Hooker, Charles W
    - Jorgensen, Lars
    - Sloan-Kettering Institute
    - Turner, Joseph Cary
    - Winternitz, M C
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1948
    - Krakaur, Richard Burton
    - Glenn, Frank
    - Cooper, William A
    - Howes, Edward L
    - Glenn, Frank
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1948
    - Harvey, Samuel C
    - Winternitz, M
    - Jackson Memorial Laboratory
    - Opie, Eugene L
    - Rusch, H P
    - Miller, J A
    - Burkholder, Paul R
    - Sonneborn, T M
    - Wagtendonk, W J van
    - Atkinson, William B
    - Taylor, Howard C., Jr.
    - Tatum, Edward L
    - Leblond, Charles P
    - Schwartz, Ernest
    - Thompson, Helen P
    - Krementz, Edward T
    - Downie, George R
    - Dougherty, Ellsworth C
    - Meader, Ralph C
    - State, David
    - Gaviser, David
    - Shringley, Edward W
    - Haven, Frances L
    - Plaut, Alfred
    - Black, Maurice
    - Twombly, Gray H
    - Claude, Albert
    - Holbrook, Mildred P
    - Mester, Elizabeth M
    - Rogers, Stanfield
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1948 March
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Harrison, Ross G
    - Little, C C
    - Greene, Harry S.N.
    - Smith, George M
    - Winternitz, M C
  - Childs Memorial Fund, 1946-59
    - Meader, R G
    - Bayne-Jones, S
    - Childs, Richard S
    - Childs, S Winston, Jr.
    - Winternitz, M C
    - Phillips, Eleanor
    - Waters, L L
  - Childs, Jane Coffin, Memorial Fund for Medical Research, 1959-63
    - Ford, Elizabeth M
    - Childs, Richard S
    - Waters, Levin L
  - Childs Memorial Fund 47th-48th meetings
  - Childs Memorial Fund. Director's Report.
  - Childs Memorial Fund. Minutes. 50th Meeting
  - Childs Memorial Fund. Minutes. 49th Meeting
  - China Aid Council
    - Bibby, Henry Lambert
    - Forkner, Claude E
  - Chini, Virgilio
  - Chovnick, Arthur
  - Christian, Henry A
  - Christian Medical Council
  - Churchman, John W
  - Ciba Pharmaceutical Products, Inc.
    - Strauss, William T
    - Walton, J H
    - Haines, T F Davies
    - Roder, Paul W
  - Cieslinski, Joan
  - Cinis, Philip H
  - Citron, Robert R
  - Claps, Francis X
  - Clark, C U
  - Clark, Eliot R
  - Clark, Eugene
  - Clark, J H
  - Clark, James
  - Clark, P Lee
  - Clark, Paul F
  - Clark, R Lee
  - Clark, Mrs. R P
  - Clark, W Mansfield
  - Clarke, B Earl
  - Clarke, Donald A
  - Clarke, Louis
  - Claude, Albert
    - Bryan, W Ray
  - Clayton, Charles C
  - Cleary, John Thomas
  - Clinical Film Co.
  - Clow, John A
  - Clowes, G H A
  - Cluff, Leighton E
  - Coates, Helen S
  - Coburn, Alvin F
    - Carter, Richard
      Typed 9-20-73
    - Kelley, Florence M
    - Clarke, Hans T
  - Coburn, William H
  - Coca, Arthur F
  - Coggeshall, Lowell T
  - Cohen, Abe, Exchange
  - Cohen, Barnett
  - Cohn, Alfred Einstein
    - James, Henry
    - Kaempffert
  - Cohn, Alfred E., Library - Dedication Speech
    - Cane, Melville H
    - Bronk, Detlev W
  - Colby, Mrs. Frances
    - Vivante, Arturo
    - Karnofsky, David A
  - Cole, K S
  - Cole, Rufus Ivory
  - Cole, Warren H
  - Coleman, Warren
  - Coley, William B
  - College of Pathologists [London]
    - Cameron, Sir Roy
    - Crawford, Theodore
  - College of Physicians of Phila.
    - Rose, Edward
  - Collie, R M
  - Collier Books
    - Reddoch, Edwin
  - Collier's Encyclopedia
    - Crawford, David
  - Collins, George R
    - CBS Broadcast: 1. The Disclosure that Viruses Cause Tumors. 2. The Preservation of Blood for Transfusion. 3. The Life History of a Cancer
  - Coman, Dale Rex
  - Committee for Resettlement of Foreign Physicians
    (see also: Central Committee for Resettlement of Foreign Physicians)
  - Commonwealth Fund
    - Taylor, Graham B
  - Compton, Arthur Holly
    - Urey, Harold C
    - Addis, T
    - Behre, Charles H
    - Gregersen, M I
    - Carlson, A J
    - Cattell, J McKeen
    - Chambers, Robert
    - Cockerell, T D A
    - Cohn, Alfred Einstein
    - Davis, Watson
    - Ivy, A C
    - Levene, P A
    - Loeb, Leo
    - Robertson, O H
    - Shapley, Harlow
    - Slakin, Susan D H
    - Sturtevant, A H
    - Tauber, Henry
    - Tolman, Edward C
    - Wachtel, Irwin J
  - Conant, James B
    - Stackpole, Stephen H
  - Conference on Viruses as Causative
    - Agents in Cancer, 1951
  - Congdon, Kirby
  - Conklin, E G
    - Amer. Phil. Soc.
  - Conklin, Ruth E
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment
    - Station
    - Savos, Miltong
    - Turner, Neely
    - Hurlburt, Allyn
  - Connell, H C
  - Conroe, Wilford S
  - Consolidated Gas Co.
  - Conway, Herbert
  - Cook, M A
  - Cook, R H
  - Cook, Thomas & Co.
  - Coombe, Reginald G
  - Coombs
  - Coon, F E
  - Coons, Albert H
  - Cooper, C Forster
  - Cooper, Philip [in re]
  - Coopernail, George P
  - Cope, R Louis
  - Copeland, Royal S
  - Copher, Glover H
  - Coppola, Frederic Giosue
    - Ahrens, Edward H
    - Blanchard, Kenneth C
  - Corn Exchange Bank
  - Corner, George Washington
    - Brown, Francis
    - Gannett, Lewis
    - Wilson, Thomas J
    - Whipple, Katharine and George
    - Noonan, Julia A
  - Cornish, Carol Burr
  - Cornwall Bridge, Conn.
    - Terrall, Joan
  - Cornwall Historical Society
    - Clark, Harriet L
  - Cornwell, Ralph T K
  - Corper, H J
  - Corscaden, James A
  - Corse, C H
    typed 9-24-73
  - Cosmopolitan Medical Club
    - Lamb, Albert R
  - Cotzias, George C
  - Coulton, G C
  - Cournand, Andre
  - Cowdry, E V
  - Cowie, D Murray
  - Cowles, Philip B
  - Cowles, T W
  - Cowley, Malcolm
  - Cox, Allyn
  - Cox, Ferdinand
  - Craig, Stuart L
  - Craigie, James
  - Cramer, W
  - Crampton, Henry E
  - Crane, E J
  - Crawley, C W
  - Creech, Hugh J
  - Creer, R P
  - Crena De Iongh, Mrs. Daniel
  - Criel, Gaston
  - Crisler, George
  - Criss, Mrs. Helen
  - Crofts
  - Cron, Roland
  - Croninger, Adele B
  - Crouch & Fitzgerald
  - Crowe, Samuel J
    - Flexner, Simon
  - Crowell, Marion B
  - Crowther,, J G and Franzisca
  - Crutcher, Katherine G
  - Crutchley, Brooke
  - Crutchner, K G
  - Culbertson, Clyde G
  - Cullington, Derek
  - Cumley, R W
  - Cumming, C N Wentworth
  - Cummings, Martin M
  - Cummings, W J
  - Cunard White Star Line
  - Cunliffe, A C
  - Cunningham, R S
  - Current Contents
  - Currier, T Franklin
  - Curtis, R C
  - Curto, Ted Lo
  - Cutler, Elliot C
  - Cutler, Max
  - Cutler, Richard
    - [Mrs. Marion Rous's Estate]
    - Russell, Mrs. Florence K
    - Waxner, Mrs. Louise
  - Cutter, William D
  - Cutting, Windsor C
  - Cuyler, Gordon
    - Leav, Joseph
    - Lurie, Max B
      - Congregation Beth Israel
    - New York Academy of Sciences
      - Conference on "Immunology and Cancer
    - University of Chicago Press
      - Kendrick, John A
      - Talelay, Paul
  - Dakin, H D
    - Cohn, Alfred E
    - Dochez, A Raymond
    - Smith, E B
    - Tenbroeck, Carl
    - Van Slyke, Donald D
  - Dale, Sir Henry Hallett
  - Daldorf, Gilbert
    - Stuart-Harris, C H
  - Dance of Death
    - Cambridge University Press
    - Macmillan Co.
    - Hutchinson, Rosa E
    - Cannon, Walter B
    - Central Hanover Bank & Trust Co.
    - Frank, Adele
    - Free, E E
    - Hopkins, J Gardiner
    - Warthin, Aldred Scott
    - Winslow, C E A
    - Albert, Henry
    - Roberts, S C
    - Delaney, L V
    - James, Henry
    - Smith, Theobald
    - Weld, William H
    - Griswold, Elizabeth
    - Campbell, E C
    - Davidson, H J
    - Flexner, Simon
    - Garrison, F H
    - Irvine, Billee
    - McMaster, Mrs. Philip
    - Packard, Francis R
    - Rose, Micleiffe (?)
    - Slemons, J Morris
  - Daniel, Peter M
  - Dannin, Albert G
  - Darbee, E
  - Darden, Frances
  - Darling, C Douglas
  - Darling, John
  - Darrach, William
  - Darrow, Karl K
    - Crowther, J G
    - Halliday, M H
      Typed 9-26-73
  - Dauney, Rigney
  - Davbresse, E.
  - David, Carl
  - Davidsohn, I
  - Davies-Thomas, Kathleen
  - Davis, Bernard D
  - Davis, Betty Faulkner
  - Davis, James E
  - Davis, Jeff
  - Davis, Watson
  - Davison, Wilburt, C
  - Dawson, Martin H
  - Dawson, Perry
  - Day, Emerson
  - Deaderick, William H
  - Dean, Henry R
    - Login, B., & Son
    - Cohn
    - Carrel
    - Avery
    - Dochez
    - Ewing, James
    - Jobling
    - Lusk, Graham
    - Norris, Charles
    - Palmer, Walter W
    - Canby
    - Park
    - Zinsser
    - Landsteiner
    - Swift
    - Ten Broeck, Carl
    - Blake, Gwen
    - Wolbach, S B
    - Davison, Wilburt C
    - Univerum Book Export Co., Inc.
    - Linkman, W
    - Campbell, Marguerite E
    - John Crerar Library
    - Hoeber, Paul B., Inc.
    - Houghton, Henry
    - Login, S Martin
    - McLean, Franklin C
    - Speakman, Edward T
    - Chicago Medical Publishing Co.
    - Angevine, D Murray
    - Cannon, Paul R
    - Forbus, Wiley D
    - Kidd, John G
    - Lucke, Baldwin
    - Oliver, Jean
    - Queen, Frank B
    - Rich, Arnold R
    - Smith, H P
    - Sprunt, Douglas H
    - Whipple, George H
    - Jennings, Sir Ivor
  - Dean, James
  - Dean, Sir Patrick
  - Dederer, E Almgren
    - Campbell, Edith
    - Duel, Arthur B
    - Vogel, K M
  - Deelman, H T
  - Dees, Sarah
  - DeForest, Alfred V
  - DeGara, Paul F
  - DeGowin, Elmer L
    - Wilson, William R
    - Kirkendall, Walter M
    - Early, J C
    - Bean, William B
    - Ungerleider, Harry E
  - DeHevesy, George
  - Deighton, Bell and Company, Ltd.
  - DeKay, Mrs. Anne
  - DeKay, Charles
    - Pleadwell, F L
  - DeKay, Drake
  - DeKay, Ormonde
  - DeKay, Rodman
  - DeKoven, Don
  - DeKruif, Paul
  - Delafield, Frederick P
    - Rappleye, Willard C
    - McEwen, Currier
  - Delano, Elizabeth
  - Delissa, E
  - Della Porta, Giuseppe
  - Delore, Pierre
  - DeMaeyer, Edward
    - Heston, W E
    - Bang, Frederick B
    - Enders, John F
    - American Cancer Society
    - Gazzo, Attilio D
    - Petrzelka, Charles
    - Weaver, Harry M
    - Coman, Dale Rex
    - Whitaker, Douglas
    - Lovely, Alice E
    - Associated Research Councils
    - Enders, John F
    - Ellis J Marshall
    - Weaver, Harry M
    - Fulbright Foundation
  - Dembitzer, Martin
    - Specht, Harry
    - Tucker, Frank
  - Deming, Harold S
    Typed 9-28-73